She's evil... and not just high school evil.
Jennifer's Body is a horror, comedy film directed by Karyn Kusama.
Jennifer, a gorgeous, seductive cheerleader takes evil to a whole
new level after she's possessed by a sinister demon.
Now it's up to her best friend to stop Jennifer's
reign of terror before it's too late.
Jennifer, played by Megan Fox.
Needy, played by Amanda Seyfried.
Chip, played by Johnny Simmons.
Nikolai, played by Adam Brody.
Chas, played by Sal Cortez.
Mick, played by Ryan Levine.
Jennifer's Body is a 2009 American comedy horror film directed
by Karyn Kusama and written by Diablo Cody.
Starring Megan Fox, Amanda Seyfried, Johnny Simmons, J.
Simmons, Amy Sedaris, and Adam Brody, the film follows Jennifer Check (Fox), a demonically possessed high school student who kills her male classmates and
devours their flesh in order to survive, while her bookworm best friend Anita "Needy" Lesnicki (Seyfried) must find a way to end her killing spree.
Working with Cody again following their collaborative efforts on Juno (2007), Jason
Reitman stated he and his producers "want to make unusual films".
Cody said she wanted the film to speak to female empowerment and
explore the complex relationships between best friends.
As a tie-in to the film, Boom!
Studios produced a Jennifer's Body graphic novel, released in August 2009.
Jennifer's Body premiered at the Toronto International Film Festival on September 10, 2009, and
was theatrically released in the United States and Canada on September 18, 2009.
The film was a commercial failure, grossing $31.6 million against its $16 million production budget, and received mixed reviews from critics,
with its dialogue, emotional resonance, and performances of the cast being praised, while the narrative and tone were criticized.
Following revelations that the film's poor marketing campaign was the result of the studio's desire to capitalize on Fox's sex appeal and gear the film towards a younger
male audience, Jennifer's Body has undergone a critical re-evaluation in the years since its release, and has been described as a feminist cult classic.
The film explores themes of high school, minnesota,
halloween, possession, slumber party.
The tone is lighthearted and dark.